<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourApp</string>

    <string name="launcher_contentDescription">launcherImage</string>
    <string name="launcher_text">Click to Start</string>

    <string name="category_historical">Historical Monument</string>
    <string name="category_restaurant">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_park">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_mountains">Mountains</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="historical_alhambra">Alhambra</string>
    <string name="historical_cathedral">Cathedral</string>
    <string name="historical_sacromonte">Abadia del Sacromonte</string>
    <string name="historical_madraza">La Madraza</string>

    <string name="restaurant_alhambra_palace">Alhambra Palace</string>
    <string name="restaurant_taquilla">La Taquilla</string>
    <string name="restaurant_ricon_lorca">El Rincon de Lorca</string>
    <string name="restaurant_laseda">Laseda</string>

    <string name="park_garcialorca">Garcia Lorca Park</string>6
    <string name="park_triunfo">Triunfo</string>
    <string name="park_almunia">Almunia Park</string>
    <string name="park_cruz_lagos">Cruz de Lagos</string>

    <string name="mountain_mulhacen">Mulhacen</string>
    <string name="mountain_veleta">Veleta</string>
    <string name="mountain_trevenque">Trevenque</string>
    <string name="mountain_alcazaba">Alcazaba</string>

    <string name="text_h_alhambra">The Alhambra is an Andalusian palatine city located in Granada,
        in the autonomous community of Andalusia, Spain.</string>
    <string name="text_h_cathedral">The Holy Metropolitan Cathedral Church of the "Encarnación de Granada"
        is a Catholic temple in the Spanish city of Granada, home to the city's archdiocese.</string>
    <string name="text_h_sacromonte">The Sacromonte Abbey, located to the northeast of the Spanish city of Granada, is well accessed by the
        Sacromonte road, which starts at the Weight of the flour located in the middle of the Cuesta del Chapiz,
        or on the way of San Antonio starting from Haza Grande.</string>
    <string name="text_h_madraza">The Madrasa of Granada (in Arabic, مدرسة, \'school\', also called Yusufiyya,
        House of Science or Palace of the Madraza) was the first university that had Granada, in Spain.
        It was inaugurated in 1349 by the Nasrid king Yusuf I of Granada. [Citation needed] Currently this
        palace belongs to the University of Granada, dedicating almost the entire building to cultural activities.
        It is also the seat of the Royal Academy of Fine Arts of Our Lady of Sorrows.</string>

    <string name="text_r_alhambra_palace">Hotel Alhambra Palace is an emblematic luxury hotel and palace
        in the heart of the Alhambra in Granada.</string>
    <string name="text_r_taquilla">In the center of Granada, near the bullring and La Caleta, Antonio
        and Paqui run the La Taquilla restaurant, a cozy place where you will delight yourself with
        good wines and better tapas made with maximum product maximum quality products. The attention
        offered and a warm and friendly atmosphere embrace you to make you feel at home.</string>
    <string name="text_r_ricon_lorca">El Rincón de Lorca - all the traditional flavor with touches of modern cuisine.
        In the historic center of the city of Granada. The best product elaborated and served in a cozy atmosphere full of history.</string>
    <string name="text_r_laseda">Laseda Restaurant in Granada: The Laseda restaurant is located in the Plaza de Bib-Rambla
        (or Bibarrambla), also known for its popular.</string>

    <string name="text_p_garcialorca">The park Federico García Lorca is a public park in the city of Granada,
        Spain, built in tribute to the Granada poet Federico García Lorca.</string>
    <string name="text_p_triunfo">The Jardines del Triunfo in Granada was in the Arab period an extensive cemetery, founded in the s. XIII.

The cemetery was surrounded by a strong wall and defended at the entrance of each of the access roads to the town by doors with towers.</string>
    <string name="text_p_almunia">Delimited by the roads Avda. De Andalucía, Calle Periodista Eugenio
        Selles and Calle Journalista José Mezcua Ruiz extends this beautiful park.</string>
    <string name="text_p_cruz_lagos">Located on the Carretera de Motril, at the height of Calle Recorder
        David Roberts, its total area is 4151 m 2.</string>

    <string name="text_m_mulhacen">The Mulhacén, with an altitude of 3,478.6 meters above sea level,
        is the highest peak in the Iberian Peninsula and the second in Spain behind the Teide, 3,718
        meters above sea level. The Mulhacén is part of the Sierra Nevada National Park.</string>
    <string name="text_m_veleta">The Peak of Veleta is, with an altitude of 3395.68 meters above sea level,
        the fourth highest summit in Spain and second of its mountain range, only behind the Teide, Mulhacén and Aneto.</string>
    <string name="text_m_trevenque">The Trevenque peak is a mountain located on the northwest face of the Sierra Nevada,
        between the municipalities of Dílar and Monachil. The Trevenque has a height of 2,079 meters.
        The top of this dolomitic peak is accessible on foot by two routes.</string>
    <string name="text_m_alcazaba">The Alcazaba is, with 3,371 meters, the sixth highest summit in Spain,
        behind the Teide, Mulhacén, Pico de Aneto, Veleta Peak and Pico Posets.</string>

</resources>
